Guide to the John Taber papers, 1880-1965.
Taber, John papers
- Legislative Related Materials, 1941-1959
  - Appropriation Committees
    - A few pieces of miscellaneous correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 86)
    - A number of loose-leaf binders, Date Unknown (Box 86)
    - Approp. Bill, L.H.E. & W., Date Unknown (Box 86)
    - Appropriations, 83rd Congress - First Session, Date Unknown (Box 117)
    - Appropriations, 83rd Congress - First Session, Date Unknown (Box 118)
    - Congressional Submission, Date Unknown (Box 86)
    - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, Date Unknown (Box 86)
    - Handful of X-mas cards in prime state - X-mas at the White House, Date Unknown (Box 86)
    - Labor Reports, Date Unknown (Box 86)
    - Note frm Hasen, John C., President of National Dry Goods Association, and letter to Taber with a statement attached, Date Unknown (Box 86)
    - Two Scrapbooks, Date Unknown (Box 86)
- Post Office Records, 1935-1956
  Includes some Civil Service Employment material.
  - Post Office, 1935-1947 (Box 146)
    Folders listed by towns circa 1923-1951
  - Post Office General Correspodence, 1935-1946 (Box 28)
  - Seven Civil Service Employment Folders, 1937-1941 (Box 46)
  - Assocacion Asucarera Cooperative Lafayette, annual report, 1939-1940 (Box 84)
  - Audit Report, Sweet Potato Growers, Inc., 1939-1940 (Box 84)
  - 5th Supplementary, N.D., 1942 (Box 84)
  - Campaign, 1942 (Box 46)
  - Deficiency Bill, 1942 (Box 84)
  - Campaign, 1944 (Box 46)
  - Veterans, 1952 (Box 28)
  - Post Office, 1956 (Box 28)
    Through 1956
  - Town Files, 1956 (Box 28)
  - Town Files, 1956 (Box 28)
  - 4th Supplementary, Date Unknown (Box 84)
  - Agriculture and Farm. Sec., Date Unknown (Box 84)
  - Air Mail, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Alton, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Amendments to be Proposed by Mr. Taber to Relief Bill, No. 1940, Date Unknown (Box 85)
  - Arthur Davis, Date Unknown (Box 85)
  - Atwater's P.O., Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Auburn, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Aurora, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Barnes, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Bluff Point, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Bologna, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Cato, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Cato and Meridian, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Cato Bank, Date Unknown (Box 85)
  - Cayuga, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Caywood, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Chapin, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Clyde, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Crystal Springs, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Deficiency Bill, Date Unknown (Box 84)
  - Dresden, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Dundee, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - East Bloomfield, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - East Palmyra, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - East Williamson, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Elmira P.O., Date Unknown (Box 28)
  - Ensenore, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Fairhaven, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Fairhaven Customs, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - First Lend Lease, Date Unknown (Box 84)
  - Fishers, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Fruitland, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Gage, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Genoa, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Gorham, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Hall, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Hayts Corners, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Himrod, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Holkhom, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Honeoye, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Interlaken, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - IRA Station, P.O. Cayuga County, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Keuka Park, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Kingferry, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Lake Bluff, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Lavanna, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Lincoln, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Lock Berlin, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Locke, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Lodi, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Lyons, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Lyons, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - MacDougall, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Macedon, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Macedon, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Macedon P.O., Date Unknown (Box 28)
  - Manchester, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Mapleton, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Marion, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Marion P.O., Date Unknown (Box 28)
  - Martville, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Meridian, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Merryfield, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Middlesex, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Miscellaneous loose material on W.P.A., Date Unknown (Box 85)
  - Miscellaneous loose materials (Defense), Date Unknown (Box 84)
  - Moravia, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Naples, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Newark, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Newark P.O., Date Unknown (Box 28)
  - North Bloomfield, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - North Fairhaven, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Northrose, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Ontario, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Orleans, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Ovid, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Owego, Date Unknown (Box 45)
  - Palmyra, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Penn Yan, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Phelps, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Poplar, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Port Byron, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Port Gibson, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Post Office Correspondence, Date Unknown (Box 28)
  - Poultneyville, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Rockstream, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Romulus, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Senate, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Seneca Falls, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Sheldrake, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Shortsville, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Sodus, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Sodus Center P.O., Date Unknown (Box 28)
  - Sodus Custom Office, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Sodus Point, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - South Butler, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Special Committee of Veterans (correspondence only), Date Unknown (Box 85)
  - Special Committee of Veterans (laws), Date Unknown (Box 85)
  - Special Committee of Veterans Administration, Date Unknown (Box 85)
  - Special Committee of Veterans Affairs, Date Unknown (Box 85)
  - Stanley, Date Unknown (Box 46)
  - Wallcott P.O., Date Unknown (Box 28)
  - Williamson P.O., Date Unknown (Box 28)
- Old Personal Files and Old Military Academy, 1934-1954
  - Bundles of Annapolis Examinations, 1934 (Box 67)
  - Agriculture, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Agriculture, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Annapolis, 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Annapolis (notices and forms), 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Appropriations, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Banking and Currency, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Bills by Mr. Taber, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Budget, General, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Deficiency, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Dies Committee, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Education, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Electricity and Rates, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Expenditures, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Flood Control, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Folder bearing clip and title, "Where to file", 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Hughes, Roland, 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Immigration and Naturalization, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Indian Affairs, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Interior, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - John Taber Constitutions, 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - John Taber Personal, 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - John Taber Receipts, 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Judiciary, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Kracke, E. A., 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Labor, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Labor and Federal Security Appropriation Committee, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Merchant Marine Academy, 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Military Affairs, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Miscellaneous, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Motion Pictures, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - National Defense, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Naval Affairs, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Navy, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Nolan, Charles, 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Post Office, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Relief and W.P.A., 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Republican Party, 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - Resettlement Administration, 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - Seneca Falls P.O. Building, 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Social Security, 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - St. Lawrence Waterway, 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - Sterling Station P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Telegrams, 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - U.S. Hoffman Company, 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - Union Springs P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Venice Centre P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - Veterans Legislation (incl. Charles D. Osborne letter, which K.J. cat., 7/67), 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Victor P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - Walworth P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - War, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Waterloo P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - Ways and Means, 1935-1954 (Box 67)
  - Weedsport P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - West Bloomfield P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - West Point, 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - West Point (notices and forms), 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - West Walworth P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Willard P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 65)
  - Williamson P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - Wolcott P.O., 1935-1954 (Box 66)
  - John Taber Personal, 1939-1954 (Box 66)
  - All of these folders seem to be 1940, 1940 (Box 67)
  - Bundles of Annapolis appointments, vacancies, etc., 1940 (Box 68)
  - Census, 1940 (Box 67)
  - Civil Service, 1940 (Box 67)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1940 (Box 67)
  - West Point and Annapolis, 1944 (Box 66)
  - West Point, 1945 (Box 66)
  - West Point Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 66)
  - Annapolis, 1946-1949 (Box 66)
  - West Point Correspondence, 1947 (Box 66)
  - West Point Correspondence, 1947 (Box 66)
  - Dewey, Thomas, 1948 (Box 65)
  - Charles Taber, 1951 (Box 65)
  - John Taber Auburn Receipts, 1952 (Box 65)
  - John Taber Deposit Slips, 1952 (Box 65)
  - Receipts, Stationery, Stamps, 1952 (Box 65)
  - Telephone-Telegraph, 1952 (Box 65)
  - John Taber, 1953 (Box 65)
  - John Taber Deposit Slips, 1953 (Box 65)
  - John Taber, personal, 1953 (Box 65)
  - John Taber Contributions, 1954 (Box 65)
  - John Taber Deposit Slips, 1954 (Box 65)
  - John Taber Personal, 1954 (Box 65)
  - Moravia Bank, 1954 (Box 65)
  - Stationery, Telephone and Telegraph, 1954 (Box 65)
  - Telephone and Telegraph, 1954 (Box 65)
- Chronological Files, 1938-1960
  - National Income and Expenditure of the United Kingdom, 1938-1946, 1947 (Box 130)
  - The Bond Survey, 1941 (Box 130)
  - Small Statistical Abstract of Turkey, 1942-1946, 1947 (Box 143)
  - War Production Board, 1943 (Box 126)
  - Appropriations, 1944 (Box 126)
  - Federal Security Agency and Office of Education, 1944-1945 (Box 116)
  - Office of War Information, 1944 (Box 126)
  - Stockpiles, 1944 (Box 126)
  - Treasury Department, 1944-1947 (Box 123)
  - War Agencies, 1944 (Box 126)
  - Commodity Catalog, 1945, 1945 (Box 136)
  - Deficiency, 1945 (Box 126)
  - Foreign Economic Administration, 1945 (Box 116)
  - Maritime Commission, War Shipping Administration, Merchant Marine, 1945-1946 (Box 116)
  - Navy, 1945 (Box 116)
  - Republican Party, 1945-1946 (Box 116)
  - Republican Women's Club of Auburn, 1945-1947 (Box 123)
  - State Department and Foreign Services (References to Red Infiltration), 1945-1946 (Box 116)
  - The United States and the World Court, 1945 (Box 163)
  - Treasury, 1945 (Box 126)
  - War Agencies, 1945 (Box 116)
  - Byrd Statement re Reduction of Federal Civilian Personnel, 1946 (Box 129)
  - Clipping on Examination of European Famine, 1946 (Box 129)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1946 (Box 116)
  - International Agencies and Activities, 1946 (Box 116)
  - Library of Congress, 1946-1947 (Box 116)
  - Memo from C. Woodrum re Proposed Mobile Fertilizer Plant, 1946 (Box 130)
  - Memo to JT on U.N.R.R.A., 1946 (Box 129)
  - Memos to JT on Lend-Lease Inventories & U.N.R.R.A., 1946 (Box 129)
  - Passports, 1946-1947 (Box 123)
  - Public Debt, 1946 (Box 116)
  - Publications, 1946-1947 (Box 123)
  - Reorganization, 1946 (Box 116)
  - Report to Congress on Operations of U.N.R.R.A., 1946 (Box 130)
  - Rural Electrification Administration, 1946-1947 (Box 116)
  - Russia, 1946 (Box 116)
  - Social Security Board and Administration, 1946-1947 (Box 123)
  - Socialistic Legislation, 1946 (Box 116)
  - State Department, 1946 (Box 123)
  - State Department - United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization, 1946-1947 (Box 116)
  - Subversive Activities (References to Red Infiltration), 1946 (Box 116)
  - Taber Statement re Reducation of Federal Civilian Personnel and Federal Expenditures, 1946 (Box 129)
  - Text of Radio Broadcast by V. Close re Taber's Cut in Marshall Plan Funds, 1946 (Box 129)
  - Veterans Administration (References to Red Infiltration), 1946 (Box 116)
  - War Assets Administration and Surplus Property, 1946 (Box 116)
  - Warehouse Inventories for U.S.S.R., Cuba, Anglo-Egyptian-Sudan, Arabia, Brazil, Egypt, Chile, Cyrenaica, Ethiopia, Iran, Iraq, Mexico, China, Holland, Norwegian, Palestine, Peru, Philippines, Poland, Uruguay, 1946 (Box 130)
  - Material in storage as of March 1, 1946, Turkish Requisitions, 1946-03-01 (Box 130)
  - Congressional Record, 79th Congress, 2nd Session, 1946-07-24 (Box 129)
  - Agriculture and Forestry in East Operland, 1947 (Box 130)
  - Agriculture and Forestry in East Operland, Maps, 1947 (Box 130)
  - Agriculture, Stock Farming, Forestry in Silesia, 1947 (Box 130)
  - Agriculture, Stock Farming, Forestry in Silesia, Maps, 1947 (Box 130)
  - Appropriations - War Department, 1947 (Box 136)
  - Briefing of Congressional Committees on European Occupation and Recovery, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Coal Mining in Silesia, 1947 (Box 130)
  - Coast Guard Survey, 1947 (Box 143)
  - Comments on Greek Marshall Plan Aid, 1947 (Box 129)
  - Committee of European Economic Cooperation, General Report, 1947 (Box 129)
  - Committee on European Economic Cooperation, Vol. 1, General Report, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Conditions in Office of Veterans' Administration, Boston, Massachusetts, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Copy of letter to Christian Herter, re Relief Funds, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Data on Austrian Agricultural Situation, 1947 (Box 128)
  - E.C.A. Figures on 1947 Wheat Production and Consumption, 1947 (Box 129)
  - Economic and Recovery and American Aid, 1947 (Box 128)
  - European Recovery and American Aid (Parts 1-3), 1947 (Box 130)
  - Financial Statement for Italy, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Foreign Aid, 1947 (Box 142)
  - Foreign Transactions of the U.S. Government, Foreign Credits, 1947 (Box 128)
  - From Bargeron, 1947 (Box 136)
  - Gould, Norman J., 1947-1952 (Box 166)
  - Grain Quarterly, 1947 (Box 130)
  - High Prices, 1947 (Box 130)
  - Housing, 1947 (Box 116)
  - HR 6777, Appropriations for Government Corps and Independent Agencies for Fiscal 1947, 1947 (Box 130)
  - Inventory of Supplies in Occupied Areas, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Lend-Lease Appropriations to the President and Accounts with Foreign Governments, 1947 (Box 136)
  - Loyalty Material, 1947-1948 (Box 141)
  - National Resources and Foreign Aid, 1947 (Box 130)
  - Office of Scientific Research and Development, Budget Estimates, Fiscal 1947, 1947 (Box 129)
  - P, 1947 (Box 123)
  - Philippines, 1947 (Box 123)
  - Proceedings of Joint Committee on the Budget, 1947 (Box 129)
  - Reconstruction Finance, 1947 (Box 116)
  - Report of Joint Committee on the Budget, 1947 (Box 129)
  - Report on 1947 Displaced Persons in Germany, U.S. Zone, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Report on 1947 Greek Economic Situation, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Report on 1947 Italian Wheat Sitaution, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Report on Greek Marshall Plan and Guerilla Movement, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Report on the British Coal Industry, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Report on World Rubber Conditions, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Rome Airport, 1947 (Box 123)
  - Silesia - A Thoroughly German Country, 1947 (Box 130)
  - State Department, 1947 (Box 123)
  - Statement of Foreign Aid, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Supplemental Budget Estimate, Government and Relief in Occupied Areas for Fiscal Year, 1947-1948 (Box 128)
  - Surplus Property - War Assets Administration, 1947 (Box 123)
  - T, 1947 (Box 123)
  - The Interim European Aid Program, Draft Legislation and Background Information, 1947 (Box 129)
  - U.N. Survey of Italian Economy, 1947 (Box 128)
  - Veterans Subsistence Checks, 1947 (Box 140)
  - Veterans, Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 140)
  - Will Dollars Save the World?, 1947 (Box 130)
  - Annual Report of the Commissioner of Internal Revenue, Fiscal Year Ended June 30, 1947, 1947-06-30 (Box 142)
  - Summary Report Presented to Committee of European Economic Corporation, 1947-09 (Box 128)
  - Minutes of a Conference Held in the Office of the Amt Fur Stahl Und Eisen of the Verwaltungsamt Fur Wirtschaft, Breite Strasse, Dusseldorf, 1947-10-06 (Box 128)
  - Text of Moscow Radio Broadcast Attacking the U.S. and Taber for Imperialistic Designs on Turkey, 1947-10-08 (Box 128)
  - 1948 Campaign, 1948 (Box 154)
  - Appropriations, Joint Committee on Economic Cooperation Administration, 1948 (Box 115)
  - Budget, 1948 (Box 141)
  - Comparative Print of Public Law, 389, House Bill 4840 and HR 4579, 1948 (Box 129)
  - Extra Copies, Statements and Broadcasts, 1948 (Box 154)
  - How to Do Business under the Marshall Plan, 1948 (Box 130)
  - HR 6801 - Text of 1949 Foreign Aid Bill, 1948 (Box 129)
  - Information on Aid to China, 1948 (Box 130)
  - Interior Department Appropriation Bill, 1948 (Box 130)
  - Investigative Report on Leander Bell Lovell, 1948 (Box 130)
  - Memos re Richard Bone, 1948 (Box 130)
  - Plans for an International Magazine, 1948 (Box 130)
  - Proposed Tax Relief Bill, 1948 (Box 129)
  - Public Iaw 472, Economic Cooperation Act of 1948, 1948 (Box 130)
  - Report of Commodity Shipments to Schools and Institutions, 1948 (Box 129)
  - Report on the Status of German Reparations, 1948 (Box 130)
  - Second Taber Statement on Above Bill, 1948 (Box 129)
  - Statements and Broadcasts, John Taber, 1948 (Box 154)
  - Survival in the Air Age, 1948 (Box 130)
  - Taber Statement on Appropriation for 1949 Foreign Aid Bill, 1948 (Box 129)
  - U.N. Survey of Economic Situation and Prospects of Europe, 1948 (Box 129)
  - Veterans' Administration, 1948 (Box 140)
  - Veterans, General, 1948 (Box 140)
  - European Recovery Program - Estimated Balance of Payments on Current Account of the Participating Countries, 1948-04-01-1949-06-30 (Box 128)
  - European Recovery Program - Estimated Commodity Imports and Exports of the Participating Countries by Value and Quantity, 1948-04-01-1949-06-30 (Box 128)
  - Letter, C. S. Dewey to U.S. Senator S. Bridges re Failure of ECA, 1948-08-17 (Box 130)
  - JT's Phone Bill, September 16, 1948, Unpaid, 1948-09-16 (Box 130)
  - Letter, Investigator P. E. Lee to JT, re ECA and Bgr. Dept., 1948-09-21 (Box 130)
  - Leg. - GPO - Publications to Russia, 1948-10-14 (Box 138)
  - Aircraft Procurement, 1949 (Box 129)
  - Correspondence on Statements of John Taber, 1949-1950 (Box 154)
  - Economic Cooperation Administration, Appropriations, 1949 (Box 141)
  - European Recovery Program, Supplement to Commodity Reports, 1949 (Box 129)
  - Extra Statements 1 1949, J.T., 1949 (Box 154)
  - Newspapers, Election, 1949 (Box 154)
  - Releases, 1949 (Box 115)
  - Robert E. Lee, Personal, 1949 (Box 138)
  - Statements and Broadcasts, John Taber, 1949 (Box 154)
  - Taber Statement on Reclamation Funds, 1949 (Box 130)
  - Agriculture, 1950 (Box 115)
  - Agriculture, 1950 (Box 141)
  - Armed Services, 1950 (Box 115)
  - Army Civil Functions, 1950 (Box 115)
  - Auburn, 1950-1952 (Box 119)
  - Commerce and Judiciary, 1950 (Box 115)
  - Commerce Department, 1950-1956 (Box 175)
  - Community Planning, 1950 (Box 130)
  - Deficiencies, 1950 (Box 115)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1950-1956 (Box 175)
  - Department of Defense, 1950-1956 (Box 175)
  - District of Columbia, 1950 (Box 115)
  - Economic Cooperation Administration, Appropriations, 1950 (Box 141)
  - Extra copies - Statements and Broadcasts made during 1950, 1950 (Box 175)
  - Independent Offices, 1950 (Box 115)
  - Joint Committee - Economic Cooperation Administration, 1950 (Box 115)
  - List of Scripts for Voice of America, 1950 (Box 130)
  - News release on Congressional Apportionment, 1950 (Box 130)
  - Report on Missouri River Basin, 1950 (Box 130)
  - Reports, 1950 Minority Clerk, 81st Congress, First, 1950 (Box 175)
  - Statements and Broadcasts, John Taber, 1950 (Box 154)
  - The Military Chaplaincy, 1950 (Box 130)
  - Two Voice of America Scripts in French, 1950 (Box 130)
  - Veterans, General, 1950 (Box 175)
  - Veterans, General, Auburn, 1950 (Box 140)
  - West Point, 1950-1951 (Box 175)
  - Air Force (secret) Statement of Real Estate and Construction Costs and Expenses, 1951 (Box 129)
  - Capitol Hill Associates (a Republican Social Club - notices, etc.), 1951 (Box 175)
  - Correspondence re Public Works Projects, 1951 (Box 129)
  - Extra copies of Statements and Broadcasts, 82nd Congress, 1951-1952 (Box 175)
  - Federal Public Housing (By Hon. J. Phillips), 1951 (Box 130)
  - H. J. Res. 277, 1951 (Box 130)
  - H. Res. 287, 1951 (Box 130)
  - Hearings on 2nd Supplemental Appropriation Bill for 1951, 1951 (Box 130)
  - House Foreign Aid BLU, Chapter X B, 1951 (Box 129)
  - HR 3790, Interior Department Approp. Act for Fiscal 1951-1952, 1951-1952 (Box 130)
  - HR 3880 - Appropriations for the Executive Office and Independent Executive Bureaus Appropriations Bill, 1951 (Box 130)
  - HR 7786, General Appropriations Bill, Fiscal 1951, 1951 (Box 130)
  - Information on Supplemental Defense Department Appropriations Bill for Fiscal 1951, 1951 (Box 130)
  - Interior Department Budget Estimate for Fiscal 1952-1951, 1951-1952 (Box 130)
  - JT Memo re H. J. Res. 277, 1951 (Box 130)
  - President's Message on Mutual Security Program, 1951 (Box 130)
  - Remarks by JT and Hon N. Poulson and Supplementary Information on Federal Purchase and Use of a Power Transmission Line and Related Subjects, 1951 (Box 130)
  - Report on Deficiencies in VA Handling of National Service Life Insurance General Appropriation Bill, 1951 (Box 129)
  - Reports - Investigative Staff Appropriations Committee, 1951 (Box 175)
  - Reports - Minority Clerk Appropriations Committee, 1951 (Box 175)
  - Rivers and Harbors Program, Fiscal 1951, 1951 (Box 129)
  - Senate Amendments to Fiscal 1951 Appropriations Bill, 1951 (Box 130)
  - Statements and Broadcasts - John Taber, 82nd Congress, 1951-1952 (Box 175)
  - Text of Amendment No. 58 to Above Act, 1951 (Box 130)
  - Voices of America Correspondence, 1951 (Box 175)
  - FY 1952, Estimate of Requirements, Acquisition and Construction of Real Property, Department of the Air Force, Directorate of Installations, 1951-05-28 (Box 143)
  - FY 1952, Estimate of Requirements, Acquisition and Construction of Real Property, Department of the Air Force, Directorate of Installations, 1951-05-28 (Box 143)
  - Department of the Army, Military Construction Project Justification Authorizing Legislation and Appropriation, FY 1952, Book 2 of 5 Books, 1951-06-08 (Box 142)
  - Department of the Army, Military Construction Project Justification Authorizing Legislation and Appropriation, FY 1952, Book 3 of 5 Books, 1951-06-08 (Box 142)
  - Department of the Army, Military Construction Project Justification Authorizing Legislation and Appropriation, FY 1952, Book 5 of 5 Books, 1951-06-08 (Box 143)
  - FY 1952, Department of the Army, Military Construction Project Justification Authorizing Legislation and Appropriation, Book 1 of 5 Books, 1951-06-08 (Box 143)
  - Clipping, Washington D.C. Evening Star, July 14 1951, re Federal Housing, 1951-07-14 (Box 130)
  - U.S. Navy Public Works Proposal, Fiscal Year 1952 - Appropriation Justification Statements, 24 September 1951, Vol. II, 1951-09-24 (Box 142)
  - Agriculture, 1952 (Box 119)
  - Budget Estimates of the Departanent of the Air Force for Fiscal Year 1952, Vol. 1 of 4, 1952 (Box 142)
  - Budget Estimates of the Department of the Air Force for Fiscal Year 1952, Vol. 2 of 4, 1952 (Box 143)
  - Budget Estimates of the Department of the Air Force for Fiscal Year 1952, Vol. 3 of 4, 1952 (Box 143)
  - Budget Estimates of the Department of the Air Force for the fiscal year 1952, vol. 4, 1952 (Box 141)
  - Civil Functions, Department of the Amy, Appropriation Bill, Fiscal Year 1952, 1952 (Box 130)
  - Conference Report, Independent Offices Appropriations Bill, 1952 (Box 130)
  - Correspondence with Auburn Office, 1952 (Box 119)
  - Department of Defense, Appropriation Bill, Subcommittee Print, 1952 (Box 141)